[
    {
        "Question": "What is an API?",
        "Answer": "A version control system used to manage your code\nA practice for dev-ops teams enabling developers to deliver frequent changes\u00a0reliably\nA framework which dictates the architecture of your program and controls the program flow\nCode that works with data and provides a mechanism for software to access\u00a0resources from the back-end",
        "Correct": "Code that works with data and provides a mechanism for software to access\u00a0resources from the back-end",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When a user tries to login to a website, he/she gets an authentication failure error. Who do you think can fix this error? (Select all that apply)",
        "Answer": "Back-end Developer\nFull-stack Developer\nFront-end Developer ",
        "Correct": "Back-end Developer\nFull-stack Developer",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In addition to SQL,\u00a0which\u00a0tool can help you access databases?",
        "Answer": "npm\nORM\npip\nCI/CD",
        "Correct": "ORM",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Build automation can automate which of the following tasks?  (Select all that apply)",
        "Answer": "Downloading dependencies\nPackaging binary code\nCompiling binary code into source code\nRunning tests and\u00a0deployment to production systems",
        "Correct": "Downloading dependencies\nPackaging binary code\nRunning tests and\u00a0deployment to production systems",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "A user has complained that the website is readable on desktop but not on mobile. Who can help solve this problem?",
        "Answer": "\u00a0Back-end Developer\nFront-end Developer",
        "Correct": "Front-end Developer",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following describe a package manager?  (Select all that apply)",
        "Answer": "Contains application files, instructions for installation,\u00a0and metadata\nA way to distribute your pre-packaged application(s)\nTakes care of finding, installing, maintaining or uninstalling\u00a0software packages",
        "Correct": "A way to distribute your pre-packaged application(s)\nTakes care of finding, installing, maintaining or uninstalling\u00a0software packages",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following adds interactivity and dynamic content to a website?",
        "Answer": "JavaScript\nGit\nHTML\nCSS",
        "Correct": "JavaScript",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these is an open-source server side platform built on the Google Chrome JavaScript engine and uses an asynchronous single threaded architecture that allows it to serve a very large number of concurrent connections?",
        "Answer": "Node.js\nReact JS \n Angular\nFlask",
        "Correct": "Node.js",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following frameworks and libraries are used for front-end? (Select all that apply)",
        "Answer": "Express\nNode.js\nAngular\nVue.js\nReact.js",
        "Correct": "Angular\nVue.js\nReact.js",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following\u00a0is\u00a0NOT\u00a0a required skill for a front-end developer?",
        "Answer": "HTML\nJava\nCSS\nJavaScript",
        "Correct": "Java",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Node.js framework doesn't provide many features for building web apps. What do developers rely on to extend Node.js features?",
        "Answer": "JavaScript\nJSON\nExternal libraries and packages\nTimely updates",
        "Correct": "External libraries and packages",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "One disadvantage of manual parsing is that string matching ignores the XML data structure. However, depending on XML data complexity, string matching might be more efficient than what?",
        "Answer": "An XML root element\nAn XML tree of the data\nAn XML attribute structure\nNo alternative: string matching is never more efficient.",
        "Correct": "An XML tree of the data",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which Node.js package can parse a string of XML elements into a JavaScript object?",
        "Answer": "Express.js\nXML-JS\nxml2js\nAsync.js",
        "Correct": "xml2js",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which web application framework is based on the Node.js runtime environment?",
        "Answer": "XML-JS\nExpress\nJSON\nAsync.js",
        "Correct": "Express",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Node.js framework treats HTTP requests at a lower network level. In contrast, Express implements an app class for what purpose?",
        "Answer": "Access a URL\nLookup web services\nMap to a web resource path\nParse through a network path",
        "Correct": "Map to a web resource path",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do you call to create a web server object to listen for incoming requests on a port?",
        "Answer": "app.listen\nhttp.view\napp.request\nhttp.name",
        "Correct": "app.listen",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following kind of task is middleware most useful for?",
        "Answer": "Performing large calculations\nRouting\nParsing strings\nError handling",
        "Correct": "Error handling",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which type of authentication is widely used for password recovery by providing a magic link to the user?",
        "Answer": "Single Sign On\nToken-based\nSession-based\nPasswordless",
        "Correct": "Passwordless",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which statement regarding the jsonwebtoken.verify() method is true?",
        "Answer": "It is used to return an HTTP status code\nIt is used to generate a JSON web token\nIt is used to return a response\nIt is used to verify a JSON web token",
        "Correct": "It is used to verify a JSON web token",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which library and module are suited for black-box testing REST APIs?",
        "Answer": "Express/TestAPI\nMocha/SuperTest\nPostman/TestAPI\nKoa/SuperTest",
        "Correct": "Mocha/SuperTest",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added\u00a0Dockerfile\u00a0to the root directory?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Containerize Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you built\u00a0your image locally?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Containerize Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you pushed\u00a0your\u00a0image to\u00a0the\u00a0IBM\u00a0container registry?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Containerize Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added\u00a0deployment.yaml\u00a0file?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Containerize Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you deployed the application to the lab environment?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Containerize Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you forwarded the\u00a0ports?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Containerize Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the main benefit of using PaaS, such as IBM Cloud Code Engine, to deploy your microservices?",
        "Answer": "Scales your microservices manually based on predefined rules and configurations\nProvides a design to run a single type of workload\nProvides fully managed deployment services to help your deployment process with minimal efforts\nEnables handling of the full deployment process by a single user",
        "Correct": "Provides fully managed deployment services to help your deployment process with minimal efforts",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the three deployment modes of IBM Cloud Code Engine?",
        "Answer": "(1) Build and deploy applications from source code. (2) Deploy container image-based applications and (3) REST APIs\n(1) Build and deploy applications from source code. (2) Deploy container image-based applications, and (3) Run Jobs\n(1) Run REST APIs, (2) Build and Run Source Code, and (3) Run Jobs\n(1) SCP. (2) TCP, and (3) HTTP",
        "Correct": "(1) Build and deploy applications from source code. (2) Deploy container image-based applications, and (3) Run Jobs",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statement is correct about Code Engine project and application?",
        "Answer": "A project in IBM Cloud Code Engine acts like a namespace so that you can create and deploy multiple applications even with the same name across projects.\nA project in IBM Cloud Code Engine acts like a namespace so that you can only create one project under your account.\nA project can only contain one application.\nYou can have two applications sharing the same name in the same project.",
        "Correct": "A project in IBM Cloud Code Engine acts like a namespace so that you can create and deploy multiple applications even with the same name across projects.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the two main application-building methods supported in IBM Cloud Code Engine?",
        "Answer": "Building container image with DockerHub and Buildpack.\nBuilding container image with Github Action and DockerHuB:\nBuilding container image with Dockerfile and Buildpack.\nBuilding container image with Dockerpack and Buildpack.",
        "Correct": "Building container image with Dockerfile and Buildpack.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the role of docker in container technology?",
        "Answer": "A software platform for building and running applications as containers\nA container orchestration platform\nA cloud tool to scan your container images for security vulnerabilities\nAn application development and testing IDE",
        "Correct": "A software platform for building and running applications as containers",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is normally the first command of a Dockerfile?",
        "Answer": "FROM\nCMD\nCOPY\nEXPOSE",
        "Correct": "FROM",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a container registry?",
        "Answer": "A container repository where your pushed container images are curated\nA software platform to build a container image\nA cloud IDE to develop container\nA cloud platform to deploy container images.",
        "Correct": "A container repository where your pushed container images are curated",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Once your microservice or web application is deployed, how can you test it?",
        "Answer": "IBM Cloud Code Engine will provide a container image reference for you to test your application.\nYou can only verify your application\u2019s running status via log files.\nIBM Cloud Code Engine will provide a URL to download your microservice, and then you can unzip and run it.\nIBM Cloud Code Engine will provide a URL for you to run or test your service or application.",
        "Correct": "IBM Cloud Code Engine will provide a URL for you to run or test your service or application.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the correct IBM Cloud CLI command to create and deploy an application?",
        "Answer": "\u201cibmcloud ce app create \u2013image us.icr.io/mynamespace/hello_repo --registry-secret myregistry.\u201d\n\u201cibmcloud ce app create --name helloworldapp --image us.icr.io/mynamespace/hello_repo --registry-secret myregistry\u201d\n\u201capp create --name helloworldapp --image us.icr.io/mynamespace/hello_repo --registry-secret myregistry\u201d\n\u201c ibmcloud ce createapp --n helloworldapp --i us.icr.io/mynamespace/hello_repo\u201d",
        "Correct": "\u201cibmcloud ce app create --name helloworldapp --image us.icr.io/mynamespace/hello_repo --registry-secret myregistry\u201d",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which method is used by the IBM Cloud Code Engine to access your container image?",
        "Answer": "From the Private container registry only\nFrom the public container registry only\nFrom the source code\nFrom both public and private container registry",
        "Correct": "From both public and private container registry",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Create and Deploy Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In the US National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) definition of \u201ccloud computing\u201d, what does the statement \u201cshared pool of configurable computing resources\u201d include?",
        "Answer": "Leverage cloud services over the open internet on hardware owned by the cloud provider\nFive essential characteristics, three deployment models, three service models\nData security, associated with loss or unavailability of data causing business disruption\nNetworks, servers, storage, applications, and services",
        "Correct": "Networks, servers, storage, applications, and services",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What tasks do hypervisors accomplish? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Scale on demand to support fluctuating workloads.\nFacilitate access to mainframes for multiple users to access the same data storage layer.\nEnable multiple operating systems to run alongside each other, sharing the same physical computing resources.\nSeparates VMs logically and assigns each a share of the underlying computing power, memory, and storage.",
        "Correct": "Enable multiple operating systems to run alongside each other, sharing the same physical computing resources.\nSeparates VMs logically and assigns each a share of the underlying computing power, memory, and storage.",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are some of the cloud benefits that make it lower-risk for enterprises to adopt cloud? Select two.",
        "Answer": "The pay-as-you-go model allows enterprises to experiment with technologies as opposed to making long-term decisions based on little or no trial.\nDiversity of standardization in how the constantly evolving technologies integrate and interoperate.\nData security associated with loss or unavailability of data causing business disruption\nThe speed with which applications can be up and running on the cloud versus months on traditional platforms, means enterprises can experiment, fail fast, learn, and course correct without setting them back significantly.",
        "Correct": "The pay-as-you-go model allows enterprises to experiment with technologies as opposed to making long-term decisions based on little or no trial.\nThe speed with which applications can be up and running on the cloud versus months on traditional platforms, means enterprises can experiment, fail fast, learn, and course correct without setting them back significantly.",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": " Which of these are full-service cloud platforms?\n\n     A.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 IBM Cloud\n\n     B.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Amazon Web Services\n\n     C.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Google Cloud Platform\n\n     D.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Microsoft Azure",
        "Answer": "A, B, C, and D\nA, B, and C only\nA only\nA and B only",
        "Correct": "A, B, C, and D",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "An IBM Institute for Business Value study says that more than three-quarters of enterprises today are using cloud computing to expand into new industries. What additional benefits do organizations find when adopting the cloud:",
        "Answer": "Improve customer experience and create enhanced products and services\nLengthen product lifecycles to ensure higher quality offerings\nAvoid having to fail at all\nContinue making expensive decisions because it often worked in the past ",
        "Correct": "Improve customer experience and create enhanced products and services",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are some of the results companies like Bitly, American Airlines, UBank, and ActivTrades achieve with cloud adoption?\n\n     A.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Better customer service\n\n     B.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Remove barriers to innovation\n\n     C.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Demand for enterprise scale\n\n     D.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Accelerating growth",
        "Answer": "A and B only\nA, B, C, and D\nB and D only\nC and D only",
        "Correct": "A, B, C, and D",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "IoT, AI, Blockchain, and Analytics are emerging technologies enabled by the cloud. What are some of the attributes of cloud computing that enable these technologies? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Computing resources can be accessed via internet connection\nThe power and scale of cloud resources\nCloud offers on-demand computing\nCloud resources are offered in a single-tenant model",
        "Correct": "The power and scale of cloud resources\nCloud offers on-demand computing",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the three-way symbiotic relationship between IoT, AI, and Cloud?",
        "Answer": "Power, scale, dynamic nature, and economics of the cloud resources\nAI consumes the data produced by IoT devices\nMaking sense of the endless streams of data from IoT devices\nIoT delivers the data, AI powers the insights, and both emerging technologies leverage cloud's scalability and processing power",
        "Correct": "IoT delivers the data, AI powers the insights, and both emerging technologies leverage cloud's scalability and processing power",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the three-way relationship between blockchain, AI, and the Cloud?",
        "Answer": "Lends trust and transparency to AI by recording the data and variables that go into a decision made in an AI algorithm.\nGlobally distributed, scalable, and cost-efficient computing resources.\nBlockchain provides an immutable network allowing members to view only those transactions that are relevant to them.\nBlockchain provides the trusted, decentralized source of truth, AI powers the analytics and decisions made from the collected data, and cloud provides the globally distributed, scalable, and cost-efficient computing resources to support both technologies.",
        "Correct": "Blockchain provides the trusted, decentralized source of truth, AI powers the analytics and decisions made from the collected data, and cloud provides the globally distributed, scalable, and cost-efficient computing resources to support both technologies.",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these are essential characteristics of the Cloud? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Fixed fee\nOn-demand self-service\nResource pooling\nSingle-tenant",
        "Correct": "On-demand self-service\nResource pooling",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following lines of code?\n\n1\n2\n3\na=np.array([-1,1])\nb=np.array([1,1])\nnp.dot(a,b)\u00a0",
        "Answer": "array([0,2])\n1\n0",
        "Correct": "0",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the value of Z after the following code is run?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n\u00a0\nX=np.array([[1,0],[0,1]])\nY=np.array([[0,1],[1,0]])\nZ=X+Y\n\u00a0",
        "Answer": "array([[1,1],[1,1]])\narray([[1,0],[0,1]])\narray([[0,1],[1,1]])",
        "Correct": "array([[1,1],[1,1]])",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What values does the variable  out take if the following lines of code are run?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n\u00a0\nX=np.array([[1,0,1],[2,2,2]])\u00a0\nout=X[0:2,2]\nout\n\u00a0",
        "Answer": "array([1,0])\narray([1,2])\narray([1,1])",
        "Correct": "array([1,2])",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the value of  Z after the following code is run?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n\u00a0\nX=np.array([[1,0],[0,1]])\nY=np.array([[2,2],[2,2]])\nZ=np.dot(X,Y)\n\u00a0",
        "Answer": "array([[2,2],[2,2]])\narray([[2,0],[0,2] ])\narray([[3,2],[2,3]])",
        "Correct": "array([[2,2],[2,2]])",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the following text file:  Example1.txt:\n\nThis is line 1\n\nThis is line 2\n\nThis is line 3\n\nWhat is the output of the following lines of code?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n\u00a0\nwith\u00a0open(\"Example1.txt\",\"r\")\u00a0as\u00a0File1:\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0file_stuff=File1.readline\u00a0()\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0print(file_stuff)",
        "Answer": "This is line 1\nThis is line 1\n\nThis is line 2\n\nThis is line 3\nThis is line 1\n\nThis is line 2",
        "Correct": "This is line 1",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the following line of code:\n\n1\n2\n3\n\u00a0\nwith\u00a0open(example1,\"r\")\u00a0as\u00a0file1:\n\u00a0\n\nWhat mode is the file object in?",
        "Answer": "read\nwrite\nappend",
        "Correct": "read",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do the following lines of code do?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n\u00a0\nwith\u00a0open(\"Example.txt\",\"a\")\u00a0as\u00a0writefile:\n\u00a0\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0writefile.write(\"This\u00a0is\u00a0line\u00a0A\\n\")\n\u00a0\u00a0writefile.write(\"This\u00a0is\u00a0line\u00a0B\\n\")",
        "Answer": "Read the file \"Example.txt\"\nWrite to the file \u201cExample.txt\u201d\nAppend the file \"Example.txt\"",
        "Correct": "Append the file \"Example.txt\"",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What task do the following lines of code perform?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n\u00a0\nwith\u00a0open('Example2.txt','r')\u00a0as\u00a0readfile:\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0with\u00a0open('Example3.txt','w')\u00a0as\u00a0writefile:\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0for\u00a0line\u00a0in\u00a0readfile:\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0writefile.write(line)\n\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Check the mode of the open function for each file object.\nCopy the text from Example2.txt to Example3.txt.\nPrint out the content of Example2.txt.",
        "Correct": "Copy the text from Example2.txt to Example3.txt.",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the dataframe df. How would you access the element in the 1st row 3rd column",
        "Answer": "df.iloc[2,0]\ndf.iloc[1,3]\ndf.iloc[0,2]",
        "Correct": "df.iloc[0,2]",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What function would you use to load a csv file in Pandas?",
        "Answer": "pd.read_csv\npd.read_excel",
        "Correct": "pd.read_csv",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How is GitHub related to Git?",
        "Answer": "GitHub is an online hosting service for Git repositories.\nGitHub is an open source tool used to create Git.\nGitHub is a main section in the Git project workflow.\nGitHub is a program required for version control on Git.",
        "Correct": "GitHub is an online hosting service for Git repositories.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Getting Started with Git and GitHub\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What type of version control system is Git?",
        "Answer": "Local\nCentralized\nRemote\nDistributed",
        "Correct": "Distributed",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Getting Started with Git and GitHub\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a repository?",
        "Answer": "A basic unit of storage in Git that cannot be changed\nA plain-text file that explains the purpose of a project\nA data structure that stores documents and source code\nA collection of user accounts that are connected to a pull request",
        "Correct": "A data structure that stores documents and source code",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Getting Started with Git and GitHub\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the purpose of a license file?",
        "Answer": "Describe the purpose of the project.\nRecord all changes made to a repository.\nExpress how people can use your code.\nEstablish secure remote login between computers.",
        "Correct": "Express how people can use your code.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Getting Started with Git and GitHub\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "On GitHub, what are commits?",
        "Answer": "Saved changes\nPull requests\nTags\nMerges",
        "Correct": "Saved changes",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Getting Started with Git and GitHub\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In the following declaration, what is the type of the variable \u2018pi\u2019?\n\nvar pi = \u201c3.14\u201d; ",
        "Answer": "float \nchar \nnumber \nstring ",
        "Correct": "string ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you define an array called array1 in JavaScript? ",
        "Answer": "var array1 = [1,2,3] \nvar array1 = new Array[1,2,3] \nvar array1 = (1,2,3) \nvar array1 = new Array((1,2,3)) ",
        "Correct": "var array1 = [1,2,3] ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does the following statement do?\n\nvar ndate = new Date() ; ",
        "Answer": "Assigns the current local time to ndate \nAssigns the current Greenwich Mean Time to ndate \nAssigns an empty string with the properties of dates to ndate\nReturns an error ",
        "Correct": "Assigns the current local time to ndate ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which DOM function returns a node object matching a div with an id value \u201cexample_id\u201d? ",
        "Answer": "document.getElementById(div, \u201cexample_id\u201d) \ndocument.getElementById(\u201cexample_id\u201d) \ndiv.getValueOf(\u201cexample_id\u201d) \nelement.getNodeById(\u201cexample_id\u201d) ",
        "Correct": "document.getElementById(\u201cexample_id\u201d) ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How are numbers converted to strings? ",
        "Answer": "string(123) \n(123).toString() \n(123).string \ntoString(123) ",
        "Correct": "(123).toString() ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the value of \u2018total\u2019 after the following statement is executed?\n\nvar total = 10 + 1 +\u201d 3\u201d;",
        "Answer": "\u201c1013\u201d\n14\n\u201c113\u201d\nThis results in an error",
        "Correct": "\u201c113\u201d",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What would the alert be, when the following code is executed?\n\nvar a = new String(\u201cHello\u201d);\n\nvar b = \u201cHello\u201d;\n\nif (a ===b){\n\nalert(\u201cSame\u201d);\n\n}else{\n\nalert(\u201cDifferent\u201d);\n\n}",
        "Answer": "Same\nDifferent\nIt would not give any alert as it is an error\nNone of the above",
        "Correct": "Different",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is the proper way to create a `for` loop?",
        "Answer": "loop (for i = minVal; i < maxVal; i++) { \u2026 }\nfor (var i = minVal; i++; i < maxVal) { \u2026 }\nfor (i < maxVal) { \u2026 }\nfor (var i = minVal; i < maxVal; i++) { \u2026 }",
        "Correct": "for (var i = minVal; i < maxVal; i++) { \u2026 }",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Select all of the following which are properways to add a `color` property to a custom `Car` object. ",
        "Answer": "Modify the code of the Car object directly to add a `color` parameter in the constructor\nCar.color = \u201cRed\u201d\nCar.prototype(Color, \u201cRed\u201d)\nCar.prototype.color = \u201cRed\u201d",
        "Correct": "Modify the code of the Car object directly to add a `color` parameter in the constructor\nCar.prototype.color = \u201cRed\u201d",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is not an event binder in JavaScript?",
        "Answer": "onclick\nonhover\nonmouseover\nonload",
        "Correct": "onhover",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the 3 parts to a response message?",
        "Answer": "Start or status line, header, and body\nEncoding, body, and cache\nBookmarks, history, and security\nHTTP headers, blank line, and body",
        "Correct": "Start or status line, header, and body",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the purpose of this line of code \"table_row=table.find_all(name=\u2019tr\u2019)\" used in webscraping?",
        "Answer": "It will find all of the data within the table marked with a tag \u201ctr\u201d\nIt will find all of the data within the table marked with a tag \u201ca\u201d\nIt will find all of the data within the table marked with a tag \u201cp\u201d\nIt will find all of the data within the table marked with a tag \u201ch1\u201d",
        "Correct": "It will find all of the data within the table marked with a tag \u201ctr\u201d",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In what data structure do HTTP responses generally return?",
        "Answer": "Nested Lists\nTuples\nLists\nJSON",
        "Correct": "JSON",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Python library we used to plot the chart in the lab is",
        "Answer": "Pandas\nPlotly\nMatPlotLib\nPyCoinGecko",
        "Correct": "MatPlotLib",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created an IBM Cloud Lite account?\n\nNote: Select \u201cYes\u201d if you already had an IBM Cloud Lite account and therefore didn\u2019t need to create it for Module 1.",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created an IBM Cloudant service instance?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you\u00a0created a Watson Natural\u00a0Language Understanding (NLU) service instance?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you forked the GitHub repo\u00a0containing\u00a0the\u00a0project template?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added navigation to the website using Bootstrap?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\u00a0\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes\u00a0",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added the\u00a0\"About\u00a0Us\" static page?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added the\u00a0\"Contact\u00a0Us\" static page?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you run and test your Django application?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": " Have you updated your forked repository with all changes? ",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Check-list : Static Pages\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a018 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have\u00a0you created a dealership list template?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Dynamic Pages Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you updated the dealership list view?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Dynamic Pages Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have\u00a0you created a dealer details/reviews template?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Dynamic Pages Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you updated the dealership list view?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Dynamic Pages Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have\u00a0you created a review submission page and template?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Dynamic Pages Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added a review submission view?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Dynamic Pages Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a012 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the value of x after the following lines of code?\n\nx=1\n\nx=x+1",
        "Answer": "1\n2\n4",
        "Correct": "2",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following operation 3+2*2 ?",
        "Answer": "3\n7\n9",
        "Correct": "7",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following code segment: type(int(12.3))",
        "Answer": "int\nstr\nfloat ",
        "Correct": "int",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following code segment: int(True)",
        "Answer": "1\n0\nerror",
        "Correct": "1",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Python, what is the result of the following operation: '1'+'2' ?",
        "Answer": "3\n'3'\n'12'",
        "Correct": "'12'",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following: 'hello'.upper() ?",
        "Answer": "'HELLO' \n 'Hello'\n'hello'",
        "Correct": "'HELLO' ",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following : str(1)+str(1) ?",
        "Answer": "'11'\n2",
        "Correct": "'11'",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following: \"ABC\".replace(\"AB\", \"ab\") ?",
        "Answer": "'abC' \n'ABc'",
        "Correct": "'abC' ",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Python 3, what is the type of the variable x after the following: x=1/1 ?",
        "Answer": "float\nint",
        "Correct": "float",
        "Title": "Module 1 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a027 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are some best practices organizations need to follow in order to protect their cloud resources and systems? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Distribute tasks, workloads, and network traffic\nAdopt a shared responsibility model \nActive monitoring for security and compliance \nRun security monitoring tools on a periodic basis to ensure security threats and breaches are flagged ",
        "Correct": "Adopt a shared responsibility model \nActive monitoring for security and compliance ",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following are key components of Identity and Access Management (IAM)? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Protecting data while it is at rest, in motion, and in use \nCloud Directory Services \nEmbedding security through the life cycle of an application \nAudit and Compliance ",
        "Correct": "Cloud Directory Services \nAudit and Compliance ",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these statements are true of cloud encryption\n\nA.\u00a0\u00a0 Encryption ensures only authorized users have access to sensitive dat\n\nB.\u00a0\u00a0 When encrypted data is intercepted without authorization, it is unreadable and meaningles\n\nC.\u00a0\u00a0 Encryption protects data when it is at rest, in transit, and in use in memo\n\nD.\u00a0\u00a0 Encryption eliminates data security risk",
        "Answer": "A, B, and D only \nA and C only \nA, B, C, and D\nA, B, and C only ",
        "Correct": "A, B, and C only ",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Identify some of the standard cloud monitoring best practices from the provided options. Select two. ",
        "Answer": "Authenticate users attempting to access their cloud resources    \nTrack usage and cost of your cloud resources and services \nEncrypt data before it is sent to the cloud\nLeverage end-user experience monitoring solutions to capture the performance of an application from the point of view of its end users",
        "Correct": "Track usage and cost of your cloud resources and services \nLeverage end-user experience monitoring solutions to capture the performance of an application from the point of view of its end users",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which job role requires the following skills?\n\n\u00b7\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Collaboration with development and operations teams \n\n\u00b7\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Containerization expertise\n\n\u00b7\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Creating custom automation tools\n\n\u00b7\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Building and maintaining configuration and deployment frameworks\n\n\u00b7\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Monitoring security and measuring performance ",
        "Answer": "Cloud Data Engineers \nCloud DevOps Engineer \nCloud Solutions Architects\nCloud Integration Specialists",
        "Correct": "Cloud DevOps Engineer ",
        "Title": "Module 5 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In what three environments can container orchestration be implemented?",
        "Answer": "Private cloud environments\n A single device \nOn-premises environments\nPublic cloud environments",
        "Correct": "Private cloud environments\nOn-premises environments\nPublic cloud environments",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the most popular container orchestration tool used as of 2022?",
        "Answer": "Kubernetes \nMarathon\nNomad\nDocker Swarm",
        "Correct": "Kubernetes ",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does a control plane do?",
        "Answer": "Maintains the intended Cluster state by making decisions about the Cluster and detecting and responding to events in the Cluster   \nShares all the resources of a node\nAssigns newly created Pods to nodes\nContains Pods",
        "Correct": "Maintains the intended Cluster state by making decisions about the Cluster and detecting and responding to events in the Cluster   ",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What component of a worker node ensures containers are running as desired?",
        "Answer": "Etcd\nContainer runtime\nThe Kubernetes proxy\nThe kubelet",
        "Correct": "The kubelet",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are three Kubernetes capabilities?",
        "Answer": "Automated rollouts\nStorage orchestration\nCI/CD pipelines\nSecret and configuration management",
        "Correct": "Automated rollouts\nStorage orchestration\nSecret and configuration management",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is automated bin packing?",
        "Answer": "A Kubernetes capability that scales workloads based on metrics or commands\nA Kubernetes capability that applies automatic changes\nA Kubernetes capability that performs container auto-placement based on resource requirements and conditions without sacrificing high availability \nA Kubernetes capability that mounts a chosen storage system",
        "Correct": "A Kubernetes capability that performs container auto-placement based on resource requirements and conditions without sacrificing high availability ",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a label?",
        "Answer": "A mechanism for isolating groups of resources within a single Cluster\nA key-value pair attached to an object\nThe simplest unit in Kubernetes\nA set of identical running Pod replicas that are horizontally scaled",
        "Correct": "A key-value pair attached to an object",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What Kubernetes object should be used for stateless applications?",
        "Answer": "DaemonSet\nReplicaSet\nStatefulSet\nDeployment",
        "Correct": "Deployment",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is Kubectl?",
        "Answer": "Kubernetes command line interface (CLI) \nOpenShift command line interface (oc) \nDocker command line interface \nCloud command line interface ",
        "Correct": "Kubernetes command line interface (CLI) ",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the function of an External Name Service?",
        "Answer": "Maps to a DNS name\nCreates and routes the incoming requests automatically to the ClusterIP Service\nDirects traffic to the NodePort Service\nProvides inter-service communication within the Cluster",
        "Correct": "Maps to a DNS name",
        "Title": "Module 2 - Graded Quiz: Kubernetes Basics\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit of using ORM?",
        "Answer": "Removes data access complexity from application code\nSpeeds up application development\u00a0\nIncreases performance\nEasier to debug\u00a0",
        "Correct": "Speeds up application development\u00a0",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When you create an object (an instance of a class) in Django, what does it represent?",
        "Answer": "Table cell\nTable column\nTable row\nDatabase table",
        "Correct": "Table row",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does Django create when you create a forward relationship?",
        "Answer": "Explicit reference\nComparative clause\nBackward access\nDjango\u00a0doesn't\u00a0automatically create anything",
        "Correct": "Backward access",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "To delete() records in a database, you call the Delete method on which objects?",
        "Answer": "Foreign Key field or Many-to-many field\nModel object or QuerySet\nFilter chain or primitive field\nChild object or lookup parameter",
        "Correct": "Model object or QuerySet",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the main reason ORM was invented?",
        "Answer": "Bridge the gap between OOP and SQL\nPromote SQL\nUse a different set of APIs for each database\u00a0\nUtilize methods\u00a0",
        "Correct": "Bridge the gap between OOP and SQL",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Multi-table inheritance is like which relationship?",
        "Answer": "\u00a0One-to-many\nMany-to-many\u00a0\nOne-to-one\nMany-to-one",
        "Correct": "One-to-one",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What method\u00a0would you use to create a subset of database records?",
        "Answer": "Filter\nAdd\nGet\nSave",
        "Correct": "Filter",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do\u00a0you specify what happens to related objects when an object is deleted?",
        "Answer": "Delete\u00a0foreign key\ndelete_related\nProtect\non_delete\u00a0",
        "Correct": "on_delete\u00a0",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Django only requires\u00a0that model\u00a0relationships be defined on one side. What is this called?",
        "Answer": "Child object\nForward access\nSingular access\n Related object",
        "Correct": "Forward access",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: ORM - Bridging the Gap Between the Real World and Relational Model\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the key elements of a Hybrid Multicloud strategy? Select two.",
        "Answer": "For seamless working, it is recommended that if you\u2019re subscribed to the infrastructure services of a cloud provider, you should subscribe to the application services provided by the same vendor. \nEmbraces a mix of cloud models and services as long as they are from the same cloud service provider \nAllows you to leverage the best of cloud models and services across different cloud providers so that your applications and workloads work seamlessly across multiple clouds \nConnects an organization\u2019s on-premise private cloud and third-party public cloud into a single infrastructure ",
        "Correct": "Allows you to leverage the best of cloud models and services across different cloud providers so that your applications and workloads work seamlessly across multiple clouds \nConnects an organization\u2019s on-premise private cloud and third-party public cloud into a single infrastructure ",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are some of the benefits of using microservices architecture? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Components facing varied amounts of load can be scaled independently \nApplication components can be developed and updated independently of each other \nEach microservice of an application needs to use the same stack and runtime environment \nEach line of code for a microservice needs to be written from scratch",
        "Correct": "Components facing varied amounts of load can be scaled independently \nApplication components can be developed and updated independently of each other ",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Serverless might not be the best fit for all applications or scenarios. Which of these attributes qualify an application for a serverless architecture?",
        "Answer": "Microservices that can be built as functions that are stateless \nWorkloads and applications that may be spread across multiple cloud environments and cloud vendors \nWorkloads characterized by long-running processes \nLow-latency applications ",
        "Correct": "Microservices that can be built as functions that are stateless ",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the characteristics of a cloud native application?",
        "Answer": "Collection of microservices working together as a whole to comprise an application \nCollection of microservices with tightly coupled UI, business logic layer, and data layer \nCollection of microservices that need to be scaled and updated in relation to each other \nCollection of microservices that are built as one huge piece of software",
        "Correct": "Collection of microservices working together as a whole to comprise an application ",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "DevOps\u2019 tools, practices, and processes are helping tackle some of the complexities and challenges posed by the cloud. Identify two ways in which DevOps is mitigating these challenges.",
        "Answer": "By fully automating the infrastructure installation process in a way that is documented, repeatable, verifiable, and traceable \nDevOps best practices eliminate the need to provision servers, build middleware, and install application code \nBy creating an automated deployment pipeline\nDevOps processes outline the development principles that need to be followed to modernize monolithic applications to cloud native applications ",
        "Correct": "By fully automating the infrastructure installation process in a way that is documented, repeatable, verifiable, and traceable \nBy creating an automated deployment pipeline",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Cloud adoption is an integral part of application modernization. What are the other two important components of modernization?",
        "Answer": "Microservices and DevOps \nVMs and Agile Methodology\nService Oriented Architecture and Waterfall Methodology\nMonolithic Architectures and Physical Servers ",
        "Correct": "Microservices and DevOps ",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "One of the key characteristics of Hybrid Multicloud is portability. What does portability mean in the context of Hybrid Cloud?",
        "Answer": "Distributing a single application across multiple providers allowing you to move application components across cloud services and vendors as needed \nA workload running on the private cloud can leverage the additional public cloud capacity when there is a spike in demand \nThe flexibility to move applications and data between systems and cloud service providers \nThe public and private cloud services can understand each other\u2019s APIs, data formats, forms of authentication and authorization ",
        "Correct": "The flexibility to move applications and data between systems and cloud service providers ",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is an attribute that distinguishes serverless computing from other compute models? ",
        "Answer": "In the serverless computing environment, resources cannot be scaled up or down \nThe serverless model requires no provisioning of servers, installation of application stacks, or operation of the infrastructure by the users/developers \nServerless computing does not require any underlying servers for executing workloads \nEnd users pay for resources as long as they are running, even if idle ",
        "Correct": "The serverless model requires no provisioning of servers, installation of application stacks, or operation of the infrastructure by the users/developers ",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which one of these statements is NOT true of a microservices architecture approach?",
        "Answer": "Developers can leverage the vast amounts of code already available as the base of an application, eliminating the need to develop code from scratch\nMicroservices find one another using service discovery, which creates a roadmap for microservices to communicate \nMicroservices breakdown large applications into their core functions to create a fully functional application\nWhen one of the microservices of an application stops to function, it disrupts the functioning of the complete application ",
        "Correct": "When one of the microservices of an application stops to function, it disrupts the functioning of the complete application ",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which one of the following statements does NOT describe the DevOps approach and process? ",
        "Answer": "Defines how people work together to build, deploy, and manage applications in a cloud native environment \nUses automated tools to monitor the performance and availability of their applications \nEliminates the need to provision servers, build middleware, and install application code\nA collaborative approach where business owners and development, operations, and quality assurance teams collaborate to deliver software continuously ",
        "Correct": "Eliminates the need to provision servers, build middleware, and install application code",
        "Title": "Module 4 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What happens if you make a change on a repository branch that you don't own?",
        "Answer": "GitHub issues a push request for the owner.\nGitHub makes a pull request.\nGitHub generates an error message.\nGitHub undoes the changes.",
        "Correct": "GitHub makes a pull request.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: GitHub Workflows with Branches and Git Commands\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "You need to run three commands to push local changes to the GitHub repository. What is the third command?",
        "Answer": "git-add\ngit-commit -m\ngit-push\ngit-remove -v",
        "Correct": "git-push",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: GitHub Workflows with Branches and Git Commands\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are three commonly used commands for working with remote repositories?",
        "Answer": "open, close, send\npush, pull, fetch\nopen, edit, push\ncreate, delete, copy",
        "Correct": "push, pull, fetch",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: GitHub Workflows with Branches and Git Commands\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When managing forks, which command can you use to fetch and merge the remote branch in a single step?",
        "Answer": "git-fetch upstream\ngit-merge upstream/master\ngit-pull downstream\ngit-pull upstream",
        "Correct": "git-pull upstream",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: GitHub Workflows with Branches and Git Commands\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which command can a repository administrator use to allow anonymous downloads from repositories?",
        "Answer": "git-rerere\ngit-daemon\ngit-shell\ngit-am",
        "Correct": "git-daemon",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: GitHub Workflows with Branches and Git Commands\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a015 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is EcmaScript or ES?",
        "Answer": "A regulated name for JSON\nA standardized name for JavaScript\nA communication standard\nA programming organization",
        "Correct": "A standardized name for JavaScript",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which feature in E6 limits the scope of variables? ",
        "Answer": "let\nArrow functions\npromise\nconst",
        "Correct": "let",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the state of a promise object when the operation executes successfully?",
        "Answer": "Pending\nConstant \nEnd\nFulfilled",
        "Correct": "Fulfilled",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "React is an open-source library created and maintained by Facebook and community developers. What is it mainly used to build?",
        "Answer": "Complex UIs\nAccessibility messages\nAI questions\nError messages",
        "Correct": "Complex UIs",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Facebook provides the Create React App to simplify creating React apps. What must be installed in order to run npx create-react-app with the name of the app you want to create?",
        "Answer": "Facebook\nThe XML editor\nNode.js\nJavaScript",
        "Correct": "Node.js",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Functional components are most useful when the component has properties, but what is the restriction?",
        "Answer": "Properties can't be passed as parameters to the function. \nProperties can't have uppercase characters.\nProperties can't be user defined.\nThe component lifecycle does not require management. ",
        "Correct": "The component lifecycle does not require management. ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What makes class components more preferable than functional components?",
        "Answer": "Simplicity \nVersatility\nRigidity \nDefinition ",
        "Correct": "Versatility",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In the Working with React Components video, what does the incrementCounter method do in the React app?",
        "Answer": "Updates a state so a component is rendered again \nStops the application\nPasses a value to the GUI\nRoutes a command through a component ",
        "Correct": "Updates a state so a component is rendered again ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the benefit of using the JSX transformation step in HTML?",
        "Answer": "Browser understands JSX\nCan be parsed by a JavaScript engine \n Converts HTML tags into React elements\nHelpful as a visual aid ",
        "Correct": " Converts HTML tags into React elements",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following features can be implemented using React Hook in functional components?",
        "Answer": "Logic\nEvent \nProps\nLifecycle methods ",
        "Correct": "Lifecycle methods ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Each Cloud Region can have multiple Zones (also known as Availability Zones). What are Zones?",
        "Answer": "Single shared point of failure \nGeographic area or region where cloud provider\u2019s infrastructure is clustered\nUnique physical locations with one or more data centers \nStandardized containers of computing resources",
        "Correct": "Unique physical locations with one or more data centers ",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Is it possible to run completely different operating systems on Virtual Machines (VMs) that are on a single host? If yes, what makes this possible?",
        "Answer": "No, it is not possible\u2014VMs are software-based versions of a single host. They cannot have different environments from one another. \nNo, it is not possible\u2014A single host can only work as one single virtual environment, and can, therefore, have only one environment. \nYes, Virtualization makes it possible\u2014 to have VMs, running different operating systems, on a single host. \nYes, Containerization makes it possible\u2014to have VMs that are unique physical entities, so you can have completely different Operating Systems on them. ",
        "Correct": "Yes, Virtualization makes it possible\u2014 to have VMs, running different operating systems, on a single host. ",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following are examples of single-tenant compute environments in the Cloud? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Transient virtual servers \nBare Metal servers\nReserved virtual server \nDedicated host ",
        "Correct": "Bare Metal servers\nDedicated host ",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these scenarios is ideal for the use of bare metal servers, as opposed to virtual servers? Select two.",
        "Answer": "CPU and I/O intensive workloads\nWorkloads that require limited throughput and performance \nHuge performance and strict security and compliance requirements \nLow cost to use ",
        "Correct": "CPU and I/O intensive workloads\nHuge performance and strict security and compliance requirements ",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are some key differences between Containers and Virtual Machines? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Even though each container uses the same OS as the host OS, it still needs to have its own copy of the OS, while a virtual machine leverages the resources of the host OS \nContainers are executable units of software while each virtual machine is a distinct physical entity \nContainers are more lightweight as compared to virtual machines \nContainers can use the same OS as the host, while a virtual machine needs its own copy of the OS, which can also be different from the host OS ",
        "Correct": "Containers are more lightweight as compared to virtual machines \nContainers can use the same OS as the host, while a virtual machine needs its own copy of the OS, which can also be different from the host OS ",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "There are four types of cloud storage available. Which storage type is ephemeral or non-persistent?",
        "Answer": "Direct Attached storage\nFile storage \nBlock storage \nObject storage ",
        "Correct": "Direct Attached storage",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What makes File storage an ideal solution for scenarios where shared storage is needed?",
        "Answer": "File storage can be mounted on multiple compute nodes at the same time \nMounted from remote storage appliances \nIts consistently high speed \nFile Storage is mounted to compute nodes via an ethernet network",
        "Correct": "File storage can be mounted on multiple compute nodes at the same time ",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these scenarios are best suited for Block Storage? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Low cost is a consideration\nApplications that need consistent fast access to disk, such as databases \nWorkloads that need low-latency storage\nWorkloads that need disk sharing between compute nodes ",
        "Correct": "Applications that need consistent fast access to disk, such as databases \nWorkloads that need low-latency storage",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these are features of Object Storage? Select two.",
        "Answer": "Object storage is effectively infinite \nStorage is attached to compute nodes using a fibre network\nObject Storage can be mounted on multiple compute nodes via an ethernet network \nYou can directly use Object Storage without attaching it to a compute node",
        "Correct": "Object storage is effectively infinite \nYou can directly use Object Storage without attaching it to a compute node",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the main benefit of a Content Delivery Network (CDN)?",
        "Answer": "Enhanced control over network traffic by routing traffic to specified resources \nSpeed, it makes your website faster by serving files from a location closer to the user. \nDistribute tasks, workloads, and network traffic\nNetwork topology ",
        "Correct": "Speed, it makes your website faster by serving files from a location closer to the user. ",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What else does the Django template contain besides Python code?",
        "Answer": "Static HTML elements\nMarkdown elements\nXML elements\nDynamic HTML elements",
        "Correct": "Static HTML elements",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Three files are created by Django after you've created a project. Which of these files is a command-line interface used to interact with the Django project?",
        "Answer": "settings.py\nmanage.py\nurls.py\u00a0\naccess.py",
        "Correct": "manage.py",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "For the onlinecourse example, when registering\u00a0the course and instructor\u00a0models in the Django admin site, you\u00a0would\u00a0write and\u00a0run \"admin.site.register(Course)\" and what other\u00a0code statements?",
        "Answer": "admin.site.register(Superuser)\nadmin.site.register(App) \nadmin.site.register(Instructor)\nadmin.site.register(Admin)",
        "Correct": "admin.site.register(Instructor)",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When you map a URL to the course view, what file do you add path objects to?",
        "Answer": "manage.py\nconfig.py\nsettings.py \nurls.py",
        "Correct": "urls.py",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Django template files display\u00a0content, such as\u00a0course names and descriptions. How is the content displayed?",
        "Answer": "Markdown\nPlain text\nXML\nHTML",
        "Correct": "HTML",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is one of the differences between the Django\u00a0MVT\u00a0and the MVC design pattern?",
        "Answer": "The\u00a0Django\u00a0framework or Django server itself\u00a0acts as controller\nMVC has a Model\nThere is no difference\nMVT has a View",
        "Correct": "The\u00a0Django\u00a0framework or Django server itself\u00a0acts as controller",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What two development tasks need to be performed to manage and determine which data will be presented to the UI?",
        "Answer": "Control the project\nModel data and create views\nAccess data\u00a0and\u00a0build tables\nSort data and\u00a0sort\u00a0views",
        "Correct": "Model data and create views",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which command is used in the Django Admin video to start the server?",
        "Answer": "python manage.py\u00a0startserver\n\u00a0python manage.py run\npython manage.py runserver\npython manage.py\u00a0startDjango",
        "Correct": "python manage.py runserver",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Django functions, like View,\u00a0accept arguments as input and return something. Typically, View needs an HTTP request object as the first argument. What does this\u00a0request\u00a0object contain?",
        "Answer": "Python commands\nDjango static files\nRead-only\u00a0HTTP\u00a0metadata\nPython scripts",
        "Correct": "Read-only\u00a0HTTP\u00a0metadata",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Django template file structure sometimes has two files created with the same name. How do you ensure Django points to the correct file?",
        "Answer": "\u00a0Add\u00a0an\u00a0identifier\nNote\u00a0the\u00a0differences\nName spacing\nAdd metadata",
        "Correct": "Name spacing",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Full-stack Django Development\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you create a ReplicaSet from scratch?",
        "Answer": "Use the \u2018get pods\u2019 command.\nApply a YAML file with the \u2018kind\u2019 attribute set to \u2018ReplicaSet\u2019.\nUse the \u2018scale\u2019 command to scale the deployment.\nApply a JSON file that includes the number of desired replicas.",
        "Correct": "Apply a YAML file with the \u2018kind\u2019 attribute set to \u2018ReplicaSet\u2019.",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What Kubernetes object adds or deletes pods for scaling and redundancy?",
        "Answer": "A Config Map\nA Secret\nA ReplicaSet\nA DaemonSet",
        "Correct": "A ReplicaSet",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which Kubernetes autoscaler type scales the Cluster?",
        "Answer": "Vertical Pod Autoscaler (VPA)\nYou cannot autoscale a Kubernetes Cluster.\nHorizontal Pod Autoscaler (HPA)\nCluster Autoscaler (CA)",
        "Correct": "Cluster Autoscaler (CA)",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you prepare your application to enable rolling updates?",
        "Answer": "Add liveness and readiness probes to deployments.\nUse autoscaling.\nSet the maxSurge to 50%.\nSet the maxSurge to 100%.",
        "Correct": "Add liveness and readiness probes to deployments.",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which rolling update types ensure 100% app availability?",
        "Answer": "Both all-at-once and one-at-a-time updates and rollbacks ensure 100% app availability.\nAll-at-once updates and rollbacks ensure 100% app availability.\nOne-at-a-time updates and rollbacks ensure 100% app availability.\nNo rolling update types can ensure 100% app availability.",
        "Correct": "One-at-a-time updates and rollbacks ensure 100% app availability.",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does a ConfigMap do?",
        "Answer": "Provides variables for your application\nProvides sensitive information to your application\nMounts a file using the volumes plugin \nVerifies that a Secret was created",
        "Correct": "Provides variables for your application",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are three ways to create a ConfigMap? ",
        "Answer": "By providing a ConfigMap YAML descriptor file\nBy using string literals\nBy using an existing property or \u2018key\u2019 = \u2018value\u2019 file\nBy adding another environment to the deployment descriptor",
        "Correct": "By providing a ConfigMap YAML descriptor file\nBy using string literals\nBy using an existing property or \u2018key\u2019 = \u2018value\u2019 file",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are three ways to create a Secret?",
        "Answer": "By using volume mounts\nBy providing a ConfigMap YAML descriptor file\nBy using a string literal \nBy using environment variables ",
        "Correct": "By using volume mounts\nBy using a string literal \nBy using environment variables ",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does Service binding do? ",
        "Answer": "Manages configuration and credentials for back-end Services while protecting sensitive data\nProvides variables for your application\nConsumes the external Service by binding the application to a deployment\nMakes Service credentials available to you automatically as a Secret",
        "Correct": "Manages configuration and credentials for back-end Services while protecting sensitive data",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the three required steps to bind the IBM Cloud Service to your Cluster? ",
        "Answer": "Bind the Service to your Cluster to create credentials.\nProvision an instance of the Service.\nConfigure your app to access the credentials.\nErase the credential configuration file after credential setup.",
        "Correct": "Bind the Service to your Cluster to create credentials.\nProvision an instance of the Service.\nConfigure your app to access the credentials.",
        "Title": "Module 3 - Graded Quiz: Managing Applications with Kubernetes\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statements are correct about databases?",
        "Answer": "A database is a repository of data\nThere are different types of databases - Relational, Hierarchical, NoSQL, etc.\nA database can be populated with data and be queried\u00a0\nAll of the above",
        "Correct": "All of the above",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Databases\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "A database stores data in tabular form only. True or False?",
        "Answer": "True\nFalse",
        "Correct": "False",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Databases\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In a library\u00a0entity-relationship data model, a book is an example of _____ and the book\u2019s title, edition, and publication date are examples of _______.",
        "Answer": "an entity, attributes\nan attribute, entities\nan\u00a0entity, properties\u00a0\na row, columns",
        "Correct": "an entity, attributes",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Databases\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statements about a database is/are correct?",
        "Answer": "A database is a logically coherent collection of data with some inherent meaning\nData can only be added and queried from a database but not modified\nOnly SQL can be used to query data in a database\nAll of the above",
        "Correct": "A database is a logically coherent collection of data with some inherent meaning",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Databases\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The primary key of a relational table uniquely identifies each row in a table. True or False?",
        "Answer": "True\nFalse",
        "Correct": "True",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Databases\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What strategy was Red Hat OpenShift designed for?",
        "Answer": "A public cloud strategy \nAn on-premises strategy.\nA hybrid-cloud strategy.\nA private cloud strategy. ",
        "Correct": "A hybrid-cloud strategy.",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which three statements are true?",
        "Answer": "The oc lets you manage projects during restricted bandwidth or availability of the web console. \nThe oc and kubectl binary offer different capabilities. \nThe oc lets you script OpenShift operations. \nThe oc lets you work directly with project source code using command script. ",
        "Correct": "The oc lets you manage projects during restricted bandwidth or availability of the web console. \nThe oc lets you script OpenShift operations. \nThe oc lets you work directly with project source code using command script. ",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are three added features that OpenShift provides?",
        "Answer": "Better management through image streams \nGood networking solutions out of the box\nBetter user experience \nMore flexible",
        "Correct": "Better management through image streams \nGood networking solutions out of the box\nBetter user experience ",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the three Build triggers used in OpenShift?",
        "Answer": "ImageStream\nWebhook\nImage change\nConfiguration change",
        "Correct": "Webhook\nImage change\nConfiguration change",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the two features of an ImageStream?",
        "Answer": "Provides a trigger capability when a new version of an image is available\nProvides content for Builds\nCreates and updates container images\nStores images",
        "Correct": "Provides a trigger capability when a new version of an image is available\nCreates and updates container images",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What three processes are performed by the Operator Framework tool set?",
        "Answer": "Package\nCoding \nTesting\nBuilding",
        "Correct": "Package\nCoding \nTesting",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the three features of Custom Resource Definitions (CRDs)?",
        "Answer": "Can be engaged with kubectl\nControl the install, upgrade, and role-based access control (RBAC) of Operators in a cluster\nExtend Kubernetes functionality\nMake Kubernetes API more modular",
        "Correct": "Can be engaged with kubectl\nExtend Kubernetes functionality\nMake Kubernetes API more modular",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What packages, deploys, and manages native apps in Kubernetes?",
        "Answer": "An Operator \nA Deployment\nA ReplicaSet\n A Container",
        "Correct": "An Operator ",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Istio, what handles communication between services?",
        "Answer": "The proxy server\nThe control plane\nThe data plane\nEnvironmental changes ",
        "Correct": "The data plane",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What provides traffic management to control the flow of traffic between Services?",
        "Answer": "Kubectl\nAn autoscaler\nA container\nA service mesh",
        "Correct": "A service mesh",
        "Title": "Module 4 - Graded Quiz: The Kubernetes Ecosystem\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a State?",
        "Answer": "A component\u2019s render function that returns data about an attribute \nAn object that contains information about the component\nA parent component function that takes a string argument \nA piece of software that passes data between React components ",
        "Correct": "An object that contains information about the component",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is used to pass data between React components?",
        "Answer": "HTML attribute \nShared state \nProp\nLocal state ",
        "Correct": "Prop",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do you use to pass data from child components to parent components?",
        "Answer": "State \nCallback\nMethod \nRender ",
        "Correct": "Callback",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When does a component lifecycle start?",
        "Answer": "When components are created or mounted on the DOM \nWhen a user clicks the mouse or presses the keyboard \nWhen the state of the component first changes \nWhen the component is removed from the DOM ",
        "Correct": "When components are created or mounted on the DOM ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do you use to pass data from parent components to child components?",
        "Answer": "Method \nState \nCallback\nProp",
        "Correct": "Prop",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which function is invoked right after the component is mounted on the DOM?",
        "Answer": "componentDidMount \nRender\ncomponentWillMount \ncomponentWillUnmount ",
        "Correct": "componentDidMount ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do you use to make a call to an external server asynchronous?",
        "Answer": "Props\nPromises\nState \nMethod",
        "Correct": "Promises",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does the postDataToServer method do?",
        "Answer": "Requests all objects in the usercollection destination \nSets a component with a user state to \u201cNone Logged In\u201d \nSends the data to the server and updates the response from the server to the component\u2019s state completionStatus \nCreates a JSON object and pushes it into the usercollection array ",
        "Correct": "Sends the data to the server and updates the response from the server to the component\u2019s state completionStatus ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the phases of a component test?",
        "Answer": "Query, Run, Resolve \nArrange, Act, and Assert\nBegin, Revise, Complete \nChai, Sinon, and Mocha ",
        "Correct": "Arrange, Act, and Assert",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the two testing approaches?",
        "Answer": "Component and end-to-end \nMocha and Chai \nSimulated and authenticated \nRegression and event ",
        "Correct": "Component and end-to-end ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following does NOT represent one of the three main Cloud Service Models referred to in the course?",
        "Answer": "SaaS\nIaaS\nCaaS\nPaaS",
        "Correct": "CaaS",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which one of the provided options is true for Infrastructure-as-a-Service?",
        "Answer": "Cloud provider manages the physical resources, operating systems, development tools, databases, and business analytics\nCloud provider configures the infrastructure which is managed and maintained by the user/customer organization\nCloud provider owns, manages, and maintains the physical resources\nCloud provider manages the physical resources, the platform resources, applications, and data",
        "Correct": "Cloud provider owns, manages, and maintains the physical resources",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which are some of the key components of cloud Infrastructure-as-a-Service? Select two.",
        "Answer": "IaaS providers manage the hypervisors and end-users provision the virtual instances\nIaaS providers deploy the middleware and install required applications on the virtual machines\nIaaS providers manage the hypervisors and provision virtual instances\nIaaS providers manage large data centers that contain the physical machines required to power the various layers of abstraction on top of them",
        "Correct": "IaaS providers manage the hypervisors and end-users provision the virtual instances\nIaaS providers manage large data centers that contain the physical machines required to power the various layers of abstraction on top of them",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following are essential characteristics of Platform-as-a-Service? Select two.",
        "Answer": "PaaS clouds provide services and APIs that help developers deliver elastically scalable and highly available cloud applications\nIn a PaaS model, the provider also takes responsibility for the application code and its maintenance\nPaaS offerings support middleware capabilities that assists developers by reducing the amount of code that must be written to expand the application\u2019s functional capabilities\nOrganizations who opt for PaaS still need to configure supporting technologies such as load balancers and databases",
        "Correct": "PaaS clouds provide services and APIs that help developers deliver elastically scalable and highly available cloud applications\nPaaS offerings support middleware capabilities that assists developers by reducing the amount of code that must be written to expand the application\u2019s functional capabilities",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which one of the following is a key characteristic of Software-as-a-Service?",
        "Answer": "SaaS services do not provide options for user customization\nSecurity, compliance, and maintenance of the software are the responsibilities of the user\nEnsure every user has access to the same, centrally located, infrastructure and application code\nSingle tenant architecture",
        "Correct": "Ensure every user has access to the same, centrally located, infrastructure and application code",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these statements is a characteristic of Public Clouds? ",
        "Answer": "Resources are assigned as per estimated need decided at the time of subscribing for the service\nA public cloud provides a dedicated pool of resources to each of its multiple users\nThe cloud provider provisions the resources and services as needed by individual users\nA public cloud is a virtualized multi-tenant architecture",
        "Correct": "A public cloud is a virtualized multi-tenant architecture",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statements is NOT a correct statement about Private clouds?",
        "Answer": "Private Clouds can be implemented internally or externally\nPrivate Clouds are suitable for workloads that require maximum control and security\nPrivate clouds can only be deployed on-premise, in an organization\u2019s own datacenter\nVPC is an example of a type of Private Cloud",
        "Correct": "Private clouds can only be deployed on-premise, in an organization\u2019s own datacenter",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of these statements are true of Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)? Select two.",
        "Answer": "The VPC infrastructure is owned, managed, and operated by the public cloud service provider\nVPCs are provisioned in a logically isolated part of a shared public cloud\nVPCs may be provisioned over a cloud service provider\u2019s infrastructure, but the infrastructure is owned, managed, and operated by the enterprise\nVPC allows all users of the shared public cloud to access resources in the VPC on need basis; it also allows users of the VPC to access resources of the public cloud",
        "Correct": "The VPC infrastructure is owned, managed, and operated by the public cloud service provider\nVPCs are provisioned in a logically isolated part of a shared public cloud",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "If an organization needs to run a highly sensitive and mission critical application with unpredictable performance and capacity requirements, which of the following models would best meet its requirements?",
        "Answer": "Hybrid Cloud\nPrivate Cloud\nPublic Cloud\nOn-premise Data Centers",
        "Correct": "Hybrid Cloud",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statements about Hybrid Cloud is NOT correct?",
        "Answer": "Hybrid clouds are only suitable for workloads involving Infrastructure-as-a-Service\nHybrid clouds can prevent lock-in to a single Cloud Provider\nHybrid cloud is a computing environment that connects an organization's on-premise private cloud and third-party public cloud into a single flexible infrastructure\nHybrid Clouds allow organizations to leverage the additional public cloud capacity when a workload running on the private cloud has a spike in demand",
        "Correct": "Hybrid clouds are only suitable for workloads involving Infrastructure-as-a-Service",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Django\u00a0class-based view needs to be mapped with a URL pattern,\u00a0almost like configuring the URL for the function-based view.\u00a0The\u00a0only\u00a0difference\u00a0is you need to specify:",
        "Answer": "The\u00a0as_config function\nThe\u00a0as_class\u00a0method\nThe\u00a0view_base\u00a0method\nThe\u00a0as_view function",
        "Correct": "The\u00a0as_view function",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Username and password can be received from a user via a login HTML template. Which HTTP method is used to sent username/password to the onlinecourse login view, in order to authenticate the user?",
        "Answer": "GET request\nDELETE\u00a0request\u00a0\nPOST request\u00a0\n\u00a0None of the above",
        "Correct": "POST request\u00a0",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In the Django Bootstrap video, a course index page is designed that contains courses represented as cards. The multiple course cards are then added to a container. How are the multiple course cards managed?",
        "Answer": "Shuffled \nAdded to a table\nWrapped in a card deck\nPlaced in a list",
        "Correct": "Wrapped in a card deck",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Django provides a default staticfiles app that collects all static files in a single directory. You can move all static files to this directory when you deploy your app to a production web server. There are several steps to do this. What call do you make in the last step?",
        "Answer": "STATIC_ROOT\nRun \u2018collectstatic\u2019\u00a0command line\nSTATIC_URL\nRun \u201cimportstatic\u201d\u00a0command line",
        "Correct": "Run \u2018collectstatic\u2019\u00a0command line",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ASGI is another web server interface that Django apps support. What is the main difference between WSGI and ASGI?",
        "Answer": "ASGI supports Python\n\u00a0ASGI supports asynchronous code\nThere is no difference\nWSGI supports Python",
        "Correct": "\u00a0ASGI supports asynchronous code",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which type of view was created to address view extensibility and reusability?",
        "Answer": "Function-based view\nClass-based view\nMethod-based view\nHTTP-based view",
        "Correct": "Class-based view",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Does authorization occur before, after, or during the authentication\u00a0process?",
        "Answer": "During authentication\nBefore authentication\nAuthentication\u00a0doesn't\u00a0affect authorization\nAfter authentication",
        "Correct": "After authentication",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How can you use Bootstrap CSS style classes without\u00a0manually downloading and importing\u00a0it?",
        "Answer": "Link to\u00a0the\u00a0Bootstrap web page\u00a0before\u00a0you develop your webpage\nAdd\u00a0a\u00a0link to\u00a0the\u00a0latest Bootstrap version\u00a0into\u00a0the\u00a0head element\u00a0of your\u00a0HTML template\u00a0\nCopy & paste\u00a0the CSS style classes\nYou must download Bootstrap",
        "Correct": "Add\u00a0a\u00a0link to\u00a0the\u00a0latest Bootstrap version\u00a0into\u00a0the\u00a0head element\u00a0of your\u00a0HTML template\u00a0",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Django apps can have app-specific static files but can also have external static files. Where do you define the directories for external static files, so you can find\u00a0them?",
        "Answer": "In the STATICFILES_DIRS list in settings.py file\nIn the PROPERTIES list in manage.py\nIn STATIC list in manage.py file\nIn EX_DIRS list in settings.py file",
        "Correct": "In the STATICFILES_DIRS list in settings.py file",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "WSGI is the main Python standard for communicating between web servers and applications. To make Django apps work with WSGI the\u00a0startproject\u00a0command line creates a file that declares an application callable by default. What is this file\u00a0named?",
        "Answer": "sgi.py\ngiws.py\ndjango.py\nwsgi.py",
        "Correct": "wsgi.py",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Consolidate and Deploy Your Django App\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJul 2, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Do containers have to be on a specific operating system or platform?",
        "Answer": "No, containers work on many types of operating systems and platforms.\nYes, containers only work on Linux-based operating systems and platforms.\nYes, containers only work on Windows-based operating systems and platforms.\nNo, containers don\u2019t run on operating systems or platforms.",
        "Correct": "No, containers work on many types of operating systems and platforms.",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How are digital containers like shipping containers?",
        "Answer": "Digital containers must be welded to computer motherboards, just like shipping containers must be welded.\nBoth digital and shipping containers have to travel internationally.\nDigital containers are not like shipping containers.\nContainer size and specs are standardized, which makes them easier to move around.",
        "Correct": "Container size and specs are standardized, which makes them easier to move around.",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What applications are a good fit for Docker?",
        "Answer": "Applications that require flexible scaling and portability \nApplications with rich GUI features\nApplications that need a lot of security\nApplications with high performance requirements",
        "Correct": "Applications that require flexible scaling and portability ",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are three parts of Docker\u2019s underlying technology? ",
        "Answer": "Linux kernel features\nGitHub\nNamespaces\nThe Go programming language",
        "Correct": "Linux kernel features\nNamespaces\nThe Go programming language",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What Docker features create a container image?",
        "Answer": "The image command and a Dockerfile\nThe run command and a Dockerfile\nThe build command and a Dockerfile\nThe copy command and an existing image",
        "Correct": "The build command and a Dockerfile",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the steps used to create and run containers?",
        "Answer": "Create a Dockerfile and use it with the pull command to create a running container.\nCreate a Dockerfile, use it to create a container image, and then use the container image to create a running container.\nCreate a container image, use it to create a Dockerfile, and then use the Dockerfile to create a running container.\nInput the container image name and tag.",
        "Correct": "Create a Dockerfile, use it to create a container image, and then use the container image to create a running container.",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the function of the Docker \u2018run\u2019 command?",
        "Answer": "Creates a container from an image\nLists all images, repositories, tags, and sizes\nStores images in a configured registry\nRetrieves images from a configured registry",
        "Correct": "Creates a container from an image",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a Docker container?",
        "Answer": "A read-only template\nA method of isolating communication\nA persistent set of data that can be transferred\nA runnable instance of an image",
        "Correct": "A runnable instance of an image",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are volumes and bind mounts used for in Docker?",
        "Answer": "Persisting data\nErasing data\nIsolating communication\nConnecting to external storage platforms",
        "Correct": "Persisting data",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does the Docker client-server architecture provide?",
        "Answer": "Cloud storage\nCode checking\nAn application environment\nA communication channel",
        "Correct": "An application environment",
        "Title": "Module 1 - Graded Quiz: Containers and Containerization\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is an advantage of using Hooks in a React application?",
        "Answer": "Code used to write Hooks is complicated\nHooks enable you to write a functional component without state \nHooks can only be called inside React function components \nYou can handle events and logics in functional components without using classes",
        "Correct": "You can handle events and logics in functional components without using classes",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which standard Hook is used to manage Redux state changes?",
        "Answer": "useReducer\nuseState\nuseContext\nuseEffect",
        "Correct": "useReducer",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a characteristic of an uncontrolled input?",
        "Answer": "Props take current value and notify changes \nA parent component controls the changes\nAllows the browser to handle most of the form elements \nFunctions govern passing of data ",
        "Correct": "Allows the browser to handle most of the form elements ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What helps developers in developing a React application using Redux?",
        "Answer": "Redux enhances the state prediction factor \nRedux reloads the whole page when state changes  \nIn Redux, individual components handle their own state \nRedux helps in creating user interface elements",
        "Correct": "Redux enhances the state prediction factor ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In which application scenarios is Redux used?",
        "Answer": "Big application where state needs to be managed\nIn an application where all props associated to a component are utilized\nOnly in local applications to manage state of components\nIn applications with single state mapping to a single container component",
        "Correct": "Big application where state needs to be managed",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are Actions?",
        "Answer": "An object that updates the store \nAn object that performs changes to the application state\nAn object that contains the current Redux application state \nAn object that stores information about the user event",
        "Correct": "An object that stores information about the user event",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the function of the store?",
        "Answer": "A Store can dispatch and receive actions \nA store can perform any changes to the application state \nA store contains a type field\nA store describes what happened ",
        "Correct": "A Store can dispatch and receive actions ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Why is middleware required in Redux React applications?",
        "Answer": "To restore the synchronous data flow \nTo use asynchronous operations\nTo make actions faster\nTo compute the new state",
        "Correct": "To use asynchronous operations",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which middleware uses ES6 Generators to enable async operations?",
        "Answer": "Thunk\nPromise-based\nAsync/Await\nSaga",
        "Correct": "Saga",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which element in the Redux data flow generates the modified state based on the dispatched action?",
        "Answer": "Reducer \nUI\nStore\nAction creator",
        "Correct": "Reducer ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which phase of the Twelve-Factor Methodology contains Port binding?",
        "Answer": "Configure\nCode\nDeploy\nOperate",
        "Correct": "Deploy",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What makes an application concurrent?",
        "Answer": "It should have a minimal process start time\nIt should contain the same backend services across environments\nIt should store config in environment variables\nIt should be stateless",
        "Correct": "It should be stateless",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In a microservice architecture, you should",
        "Answer": "Use a different technology stack for each service\nCreate interdependency among services\nScale all services together\nDeploy all services together",
        "Correct": "Use a different technology stack for each service",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Select the correct answer that completes this sentence: \n\nMonolith application has __________ components. ",
        "Answer": "Scalable\nInterconnected\nIndependent\nReusable",
        "Correct": "Interconnected",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which component of services design in an SOA architecture defines how the service provider and service consumer should interact?",
        "Answer": "Implementation\n Interface\nContract\nOwn storage",
        "Correct": "Contract",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the purpose of Backend For Frontend?",
        "Answer": "Refactoring in stages\nService discovery\nLoading one interface that never reloads\nCustomized user experiences",
        "Correct": "Customized user experiences",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the purpose of the Strangler pattern?",
        "Answer": "Supports refactoring in stages\nSimplifies the front-end experience\nCombine functional domains\nHelps with third-party API integrations",
        "Correct": "Supports refactoring in stages",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Larger services should be broken into smaller services when:",
        "Answer": "Common data model becomes overly complex\nAutomation is required\nFunctional reusability is required\nRefactoring is required",
        "Correct": "Common data model becomes overly complex",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the requirement of Microservices?",
        "Answer": "Manual deployment process\nIndependent storage\nIts own implementation of auxiliary services like loggings, security, throttling, and so on\nCoarse-grained functionality",
        "Correct": "Independent storage",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the requirement of a development and production environment?",
        "Answer": "Different dependencies\nDifferent source control\nSimilar backing services across the environments.\nEmbedded access details in code",
        "Correct": "Similar backing services across the environments.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Introduction to Microservices\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the correct syntax for inserting data into a table\u00a0named\u00a0Members?",
        "Answer": "INSERT INTO MEMBERS\n\n\u00a0          (MEMBER_ID, LASTNAME, FIRSTNAME)\n\n      VALUES (MEMBER_ID is 345DT2000, LASTNAME is Smith, FIRSTNAME is Charles)\nINSERT INTO\u00a0MEMBERS\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 (MEMBER_ID, LASTNAME, FIRSTNAME)\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 VALUES\u00a0(\u20181432\u2019, \u2018Smith\u2019,\u00a0\u2018Charles\u2019)\u00a0\nINSERT INTO MEMBERS\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 (MEMBER_ID, LASTNAME, FIRSTNAME, OCCUPATION)\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 VALUES (\u20181432\u2019, \u2018Smith\u2019, \u2018Charles\u2019)\u00a0\n\u00a0INSERT MEMBERS\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 (MEMBER_ID, LASTNAME, FIRSTNAME)\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 VALUES (\u20181432\u2019, \u2018Smith\u2019, \u2018Charles\u2019)",
        "Correct": "INSERT INTO\u00a0MEMBERS\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 (MEMBER_ID, LASTNAME, FIRSTNAME)\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 VALUES\u00a0(\u20181432\u2019, \u2018Smith\u2019,\u00a0\u2018Charles\u2019)\u00a0",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Basic SQL Statements\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When\u00a0using the DELETE statement to remove data from a database, what does the WHERE\u00a0clause\u00a0do?",
        "Answer": "It\u00a0specifies\u00a0where to find the data to delete, by column number and row number.\nIt\u00a0specifies\u00a0the\u00a0server\u00a0where the database is\u00a0located.\u00a0\nIt indicates the condition under which the data should be\u00a0deleted; for example, which rows should have their contents deleted.\u00a0\nIt\u00a0limits the amount of data that is deleted to a certain number of characters.",
        "Correct": "It indicates the condition under which the data should be\u00a0deleted; for example, which rows should have their contents deleted.\u00a0",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Basic SQL Statements\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "A single INSERT statement can be used to insert multiple rows in a table. True or\u00a0False?",
        "Answer": "True\nFalse",
        "Correct": "True",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Basic SQL Statements\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which SELECT statement eliminates duplicates in the result set?",
        "Answer": "SELECT country FROM author ORDER BY 1\nSELECT\u00a0DISTINCT(country) FROM author\nSELECT country FROM author LIMIT DUPLICATES\nNone of the above\u00a0\u00a0",
        "Correct": "SELECT\u00a0DISTINCT(country) FROM author",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Basic SQL Statements\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The SELECT statement is called a query, and the output we get from executing the query is called a result set.\u00a0True or False?",
        "Answer": "True\nFalse",
        "Correct": "True",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Basic SQL Statements\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a010 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is a back-end technology?",
        "Answer": "CSS\nHTML\nWeb API\nBrowser",
        "Correct": "Web API",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What quality makes it possible for you to run JavaScript applications without compiling?",
        "Answer": "JavaScript is an interpreted language.\nAll modern browsers support JavaScript.\nYou can use a text editor to develop JavaScript applications.\nThe language syntax resembles Java.",
        "Correct": "JavaScript is an interpreted language.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following applications intercepts the call when JavaScript sends a web service request to the Node.js server?",
        "Answer": "Enterprise Java\nJSON\nREST Web Service\nCSS",
        "Correct": "REST Web Service",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is a difference between ES and CommonJS modules?",
        "Answer": "CommonJS is a JavaScript language whereas ES is a module specification\nCommonJS modules are written in JavaScript whereas ES modules are not\nCommonJS module files use a .mjs extension whereas ES modules use .js\n ES modules use the import() statement whereas CommonJS modules use require().  ",
        "Correct": " ES modules use the import() statement whereas CommonJS modules use require().  ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you handle operation results with Node.js?",
        "Answer": "Use blocking on asynchronous I/O operations\nSpecify a relative path to the Node.js script from the module directory\nCreate an instance of a web server application\nWrite callback functions to handle results when the operations complete",
        "Correct": "Write callback functions to handle results when the operations complete",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do you use the http.createServer function for?",
        "Answer": "To develop an anonymous function to handle requests and responses\nTo specify a main script for your module\nTo import a Node.js module\nTo create an instance of a web server",
        "Correct": "To create an instance of a web server",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which core Node.js module can be used for input and output (I/O)?",
        "Answer": "fs\nURL\nutil\nhttp",
        "Correct": "fs",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is an aspect of Node Package Manager (NPM)?",
        "Answer": "It manages the versioning of source code\nIt creates a package.json file in the project\u2019s root directory\nIt writes metadata to a package.json file\nIt functions as a command line interface for installing packages",
        "Correct": "It functions as a command line interface for installing packages",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do you use the require function for?",
        "Answer": "To develop an anonymous function to handle requests and responses\nTo create an instance of a web server\nTo specify a main script for your module\nTo import a Node.js module",
        "Correct": "To import a Node.js module",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What happens when a module does not have a package.json file?",
        "Answer": "Node.js assumes that the main class is named index.js.\nThe require statement assumes that scripts have a file extension of js.\nThe relative path to the Node.js script changes to an absolute path from the module directory.\nThere is no module manifest.",
        "Correct": "Node.js assumes that the main class is named index.js.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following ways of applying CSS has the highest priority, and will override the other ways? ",
        "Answer": "An external CSS file\nWhichever way is specified in the HTML markup\nInline CSS, placed directly in each HTML element\nInternal CSS, applied within the \u201c<style>\u201d attribute in HTML markup",
        "Correct": "Inline CSS, placed directly in each HTML element",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Select all of the following which are true in describing a fluid and/or fixed layout.",
        "Answer": "Fluid layouts should always be used when designing a website\nElements in a fluidlayout have flexible widths and heights\nA fixed layoutspecifies element sizes using percentages\nFixed layouts are independent of screen sizes, and their values do not change",
        "Correct": "Elements in a fluidlayout have flexible widths and heights\nFixed layouts are independent of screen sizes, and their values do not change",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following tags define a caption for a < fieldset > element? ",
        "Answer": "<legend>\n<title>\n<label>\n<caption>",
        "Correct": "<legend>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a modifier?",
        "Answer": "A method used to modify CSS styling applied to an HTML element\nA type of button which allows you to modify content in a form\nA special class modifies the appearance of elements by applying a CSS attribute based on the condition described\nThe term used to refer to a JavaScript class which updates content on a webpage",
        "Correct": "A special class modifies the appearance of elements by applying a CSS attribute based on the condition described",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which semantic tag is used to display any content which is indirectlyrelated to the main content of the document?",
        "Answer": "<article>\n<section>\n<details>\n<aside>",
        "Correct": "<aside>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which type of input control would be most apt for selecting heightin a form?",
        "Answer": "number\nrange\nlist\ntel",
        "Correct": "number",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of a Component Framework?",
        "Answer": "Download size of HTML markup is increased\nIt is more difficult to maintain a uniform style throughout the website\nComponents are limited only to what the framework provides\nHTML markup is more verbose since styles are mixed with content",
        "Correct": "Components are limited only to what the framework provides",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to represent an independent item of content in a document, which can be meaningful on its own? ",
        "Answer": "<div>\n<article>\n<details>\n<section>",
        "Correct": "<article>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which element defines a caption for the <figure> element? ",
        "Answer": "<label> \n<title> \n<figcaption> \n<legend> ",
        "Correct": "<figcaption> ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which type of input control can be used to accept only numbers in a form? ",
        "Answer": "integer\nnumber\ntel\ndigit",
        "Correct": "number",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created\u00a0a superuser\u00a0for\u00a0your Django\u00a0Admin site?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "User Management Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a016 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added the\u00a0user login/logout and signup menu items to the navigation bar?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "User Management Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a016 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added\u00a0a login view to handle login request?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "User Management Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a016 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added\u00a0a logout view to handle logout request?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "User Management Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a016 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added\u00a0a signup Django template?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "User Management Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a016 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added\u00a0a signup view to handle signup request?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "User Management Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a016 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you added CI/CD to your project using GitHub actions?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "User Management Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a016 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you run code linting and explored its results?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "User Management Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a016 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the tuple A=((1),[2,3],[4]), that contains a tuple and list. What is the result of the following operation A[2] ?",
        "Answer": "[4]\n[2,3]\n1",
        "Correct": "[4]",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the tuple A=((11,12),[21,22]), that contains a tuple and list. What is the result of the following operation A[0][1]?",
        "Answer": "21\n11\n12",
        "Correct": "12",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The method append does the following:",
        "Answer": "adds one element to a list\nmerges two lists or insert multiple elements to a list ",
        "Correct": "adds one element to a list",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the following list : A=[\"hard rock\",10,1.2]\n\nWhat will list A contain after the following command is run: del(A[0]) ?",
        "Answer": "[10,1.2]\n[\"hard rock\",10,1.2]\n[\"hard rock\",10]",
        "Correct": "[10,1.2]",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "If A is a list what does the following syntax do: B=A[:] ?",
        "Answer": "assigns list A to list B\nvariable B references a new copy or clone of the original list A",
        "Correct": "variable B references a new copy or clone of the original list A",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following: len((\"disco\",10)) ?",
        "Answer": "2\n6\n5",
        "Correct": "2",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the following dictionary:\n\n{ \"The Bodyguard\":\"1992\", \"Saturday Night Fever\":\"1977\"}\n\nselect  the values",
        "Answer": "\"1977\"\n\"1992\"\n\"The Bodyguard\"\n \"Saturday Night Fever\"",
        "Correct": "\"1977\"\n\"1992\"",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The variable  release_year_dict is a Python Dictionary, what is the result of applying the following method: release_year_dict.keys() ?",
        "Answer": "retrieve the keys of the dictionary\n retrieves, the values of the dictionary ",
        "Correct": "retrieve the keys of the dictionary",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the Set: V={'A','B'}, what is the result of V.add('C')?",
        "Answer": "{'A','B'}\n{'A','B','C'}\nerror ",
        "Correct": "{'A','B','C'}",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following: '1' in {'1','2'} ?",
        "Answer": "False\nTrue",
        "Correct": "True",
        "Title": "Module 2 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When slicing in Python what does the \u201c0\u201d in this statement [0:2] specify?",
        "Answer": "It specifies the step of the slicing\nIt specifies the position to start the slice\nIt specifies the position to end the slice",
        "Correct": "It specifies the position to start the slice",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "If var = \u201c01234567\u201d what Python statement would print out only the even elements?",
        "Answer": "print(var[::1])\nprint(var[::3])\nprint(var[::2]) ",
        "Correct": "print(var[::2]) ",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the string Name=\u201dEMILY\u201d, what statement would return the index of 3?",
        "Answer": "Name.find(\"L\")\nName.find(\"Y\")\nName.find(\"M\")",
        "Correct": "Name.find(\"L\")",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Python what data type is used to represent text and not numbers?",
        "Answer": "int\nfloat\nstr",
        "Correct": "str",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following code segment: int(3.99)",
        "Answer": "3.99\n4\n3",
        "Correct": "3",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What following code segment would produce an output of \u201c0\u201d?",
        "Answer": "1//2\n1/2",
        "Correct": "1//2",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Python 3, what is the type of the variable x after the following: x=2/2 ?",
        "Answer": "float\nint",
        "Correct": "float",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Whatdata type must have unique keys?",
        "Answer": "List\nDictionary\nTuple",
        "Correct": "Dictionary",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a tuple?",
        "Answer": "A collection that is ordered and unchangeable\nA collection that is unordered and changeable\nA collection that is ordered and changeable",
        "Correct": "A collection that is ordered and unchangeable",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following operation: '1,2,3,4'.split(',') ?",
        "Answer": "('1','2','3','4')\n'1','2','3','4'\n'1234'\n['1','2','3','4']",
        "Correct": "['1','2','3','4']",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Tuples are:",
        "Answer": "Mutable\nUnordered\nNot indexed\nNot mutable",
        "Correct": "Not mutable",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What happens with this segment of code: a=set(A) ?",
        "Answer": "It returns an error\nIt casts the list \u201ca\u201d to the set \u201cA\u201d\nIt casts the list \u201cA\u201d to the set \u201ca\u201d",
        "Correct": "It casts the list \u201cA\u201d to the set \u201ca\u201d",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "If x=1 what will produce the below output?\n\nHi\n\nMike",
        "Answer": "if(x==1): \n\nprint('Hello') \n\n else: \n\n    print('Hi') \n\n print('Mike') \nif(x!=1): \n\nprint('Hello') \n\n else: \n\n    print('Hi') \n\n print('Mike') \nif(x!=1): \n\nprint('Hi') \n\n else: \n\n    print('Hello') \n\n print('Mike') ",
        "Correct": "if(x!=1): \n\nprint('Hello') \n\n else: \n\n    print('Hi') \n\n print('Mike') ",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is an error that occurs during the execution of code?",
        "Answer": "Finally\nException\nError messages\nException handling",
        "Correct": "Exception",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What add function would return \u20182\u2019 ?",
        "Answer": "def add(x): return(x+x) add(1) \ndef add(x): return(x+x) add('1') \ndef add(x): return(x+x+x) add('1') ",
        "Correct": "def add(x): return(x+x) add(1) ",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What method organizes the elements in a given list in a specific descending or ascending order?",
        "Answer": "join()\nsplit()\nreplace()\nsort()",
        "Correct": "sort()",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What segment of code would output the following?\n\n3\n\n6\n\n9",
        "Answer": "A=['1','2','3'] for a in A: print(2*a) \nA=[1,2,3] for a in A: print(3*a) \nA=[1,2,3] for a in A: print(2*a) ",
        "Correct": "A=[1,2,3] for a in A: print(3*a) ",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What code segment would output the following?\n\n2",
        "Answer": "for i in range(1,5): if (i!=2): print(i)\nfor i in range(1,5): if (i==2): print(i)\nfor i in range(1,5): if (i!=1): print(i)",
        "Correct": "for i in range(1,5): if (i==2): print(i)",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the class Rectangle, what are the data attributes?\n\n class Rectangle(object):\n        def __init__(self,width=2,height =3,color='r'):\n                                  self.height=height\n                                  self.width=width\n                                  self.color=color\n    def drawRectangle(self):\n                       import matplotlib.pyplot as plt\n                       plt.gca().add_patch(plt.Rectangle((0, 0),self.width, self.height ,fc=self.color))\n                       plt.axis('scaled')\n                       plt.show()",
        "Answer": "drawRectangle\n__init__\nself.height, self.width,self.color",
        "Correct": "self.height, self.width,self.color",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following lines of code?\n\n a=np.array([0,1,0,1,0]) b=np.array([1,0,1,0,1]) a+b ",
        "Answer": "0\narray([1, 1, 1, 1, 1])\narray([0, 0, 0, 0, 0])",
        "Correct": "array([1, 1, 1, 1, 1])",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following lines of code?\n\n a=np.array([10,9,8,7,6]) a+1",
        "Answer": "array([9, 8, 7, 6, 5])\narray([11,10,9,8,7])\narray([101,91,81,71,61])",
        "Correct": "array([11,10,9,8,7])",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How would you select the columns with the headers: Artist, Length and Genre from the dataframe df and assign them to the variable y ?",
        "Answer": "y=df['Artist','Length','Genre'] \ny=df[['Artist','Length','Genre']]\ny=df[['Artist'],['Length'],['Genre']]",
        "Correct": "y=df[['Artist','Length','Genre']]",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the method readline() used for?",
        "Answer": "It reads the entire file all at once\nIt reads 10 lines of a file at a time\nIt helps to read one complete line from a given text file",
        "Correct": "It helps to read one complete line from a given text file",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which line of code is in the mode of append?",
        "Answer": "with open(\"Example.txt\",\"r\") as file1:\nwith open(\"Example.txt\",\"w\") as file1:\nwith open(\"Example.txt\",\"a\") as file1:",
        "Correct": "with open(\"Example.txt\",\"a\") as file1:",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the 3 parts to a URL?",
        "Answer": "Put, route, and get\nGet, post, and scheme\nScheme, internet address, and route\nBlock, post, and route",
        "Correct": "Scheme, internet address, and route",
        "Title": "Final Exam\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a01h 15m\n\nDueJul 9, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the key characteristics of a RESTful API? Select two answers.",
        "Answer": "It works on HTTP\nUnique interface for each component\nStateless communication between client and server\nOne API to access all resources",
        "Correct": "It works on HTTP\nStateless communication between client and server",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does an API Gateway act as?",
        "Answer": "A streaming service\nA firewall to protect your microservices\nA load balancer for your hosted services\nAn API management tool",
        "Correct": "An API management tool",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which syntax is used to make an update request to a product REST API?",
        "Answer": "GET /products/114?updatedName=Calendar2023\nPUT /products/114/name/Calendar2023\nPOST /products (product data in the body)\nPUT /products/114 (product data in the body)",
        "Correct": "PUT /products/114 (product data in the body)",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which type of framework is Flask?",
        "Answer": "Database\nMicro web\nFrontend\nREST API",
        "Correct": "Micro web",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which one of the following statements is true about communication in a RESTful API?",
        "Answer": "Session state is kept entirely on the REST API.\nA request can take advantage of any stored context on the server.\nEach request does not contain all information. \nResources are uniquely identified at individual endpoints. ",
        "Correct": "Resources are uniquely identified at individual endpoints. ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the potential drawbacks of an API Gateway? Select two answers.",
        "Answer": "Single point of failure\nBottleneck in scalability\nExposes the implementation details\nIncreases requests to the backend ",
        "Correct": "Single point of failure\nBottleneck in scalability",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which specification is followed by Swagger?",
        "Answer": "OpenAPI\nSOA\nWebAPI\nGraphQL",
        "Correct": "OpenAPI",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which cURL command should be used to query a list of products?",
        "Answer": "curl -X 'POST' \\\n\n 'http://127.0.0.1:5000/products' \\\n\n -H 'accept: application/json'\ncurl -X 'GET' \\\n\n 'http://127.0.0.1:5000/products' \\\n\n -H 'accept: application/json'\ncurl -X 'PATCH' \\\n\n 'http://127.0.0.1:5000/products' \\\n\n -H 'accept: application/json'\ncurl -X 'PUT' \\\n\n 'http://127.0.0.1:5000/products' \\\n\n -H 'accept: application/json'",
        "Correct": "curl -X 'GET' \\\n\n 'http://127.0.0.1:5000/products' \\\n\n -H 'accept: application/json'",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which HTTP method is used to create new data in a REST API?",
        "Answer": "POST\nPUT\nUPDATE\nPATCH",
        "Correct": "POST",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the purpose of Postman?",
        "Answer": "Uniform interface for different components\nCommand line tool to get data\nTests APIs\nTransfers applications ",
        "Correct": "Tests APIs",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Web API Essentials - REST API and GraphQL\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) defines \u2018serverless\u2019 as the concept of building and running applications that do not require _______ management.",
        "Answer": "backend\nserver\ndatabase\nnetwork",
        "Correct": "server",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Cloud provider is responsible for which of the following components in the Serverless model? Select three answers.",
        "Answer": "Network\nOS\nApplication\nStorage",
        "Correct": "Network\nOS\nStorage",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "___________ is a Serverless computing constraint.",
        "Answer": "Vendor lock-in\nIdle time\nLanguage independence\nScalability",
        "Correct": "Vendor lock-in",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Managing which one of the following is your responsibility in a Serverless computing model?",
        "Answer": "Deployment\nHardware\nCode\nOperating System",
        "Correct": "Code",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which one is the key characteristic of a function in FaaS model?",
        "Answer": "Scale automatically and independently as required\nBe stateful\nLet you define your infrastructure\nKeep running even when there are no requests",
        "Correct": "Scale automatically and independently as required",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "A _________ is an independent unit of execution and deployment in the Serverless Framework.",
        "Answer": "Function\nResource\nService\nEvent",
        "Correct": "Function",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the responsibility of the Front End in a Serverless Architecture?",
        "Answer": "Provide scaling\nStore data\nHost static content and scripts\nHost business logic",
        "Correct": "Host static content and scripts",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is an example of post-processing in the Serverless Reference Architecture?",
        "Answer": "You could provide user registration and authentication\nYou could use messaging to notify multiple subscribers\nYou could apply artificial intelligence or image recognition to upload images\nYou enable access to backend",
        "Correct": "You could apply artificial intelligence or image recognition to upload images",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is the key characteristic of IBM Cloud Functions?",
        "Answer": "No debugging capabilities\nLimited integration options\nNo disaster recovery\nCost-Effective and Highly Available",
        "Correct": "Cost-Effective and Highly Available",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Knative platform is offered by which service provider?",
        "Answer": "Offered by Google\nOffered by Microsoft Azure\nOpen-source option for Serverless\nOffered by Amazon AWS",
        "Correct": "Open-source option for Serverless",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz: Serverless Overview\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The prefix to the filename where you write the test cases is:",
        "Answer": "test\nIt has not prefix\nunit_test\nfunction_test",
        "Correct": "test",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The python code will throw runtime error if pylint is not run before executing the file. ",
        "Answer": "False\nTrue",
        "Correct": "False",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In accordance with pylint which of the following is valid method name",
        "Answer": "getUserName()\nget_user_name\nGetUserName\nGET_USER_NAME",
        "Correct": "get_user_name",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Your code has the following method.\n\ndef returnString():\n\n    return \"Hello\"\n\nWhat will be the outcome of the test?\n\nassertNotEqual(returnString(),\"How are you\",\"They are equal\")",
        "Answer": "The test will pass.\nThe test will fail.\nThe code will throw runtime error as the values are not equal\nThe test will not run as the method name does not qualify in static code analysis.",
        "Correct": "The test will pass.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "To package a python script in a package to be able to import and use it, which of the following is required.",
        "Answer": "A folder with server.py\nThe python script should be packaged in a directory with __init__.py in the same directory\nimport sys  as the first line of code in the python script.\nThe methods in the script should be defined as public method",
        "Correct": "The python script should be packaged in a directory with __init__.py in the same directory",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is correct about Flask?",
        "Answer": "It is a full-stack application framework\nIt is a micro web framework\nIt is a database framework\nIt is an external Java framework",
        "Correct": "It is a micro web framework",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following methods are supported in an API endpoint created with Flask?\n\n1. GET\n\n2. AUTHENTICATE\n\n3. POST\n\n4. DELETE",
        "Answer": "Only 1 and 4\nOnly 1,3 and 4\nOnly 1,2 and 3\nAll 4 are supported.",
        "Correct": "Only 1,3 and 4",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the below line of code referred to as?\n\n@app.route(\"/name\")",
        "Answer": "Method definition\nRoute decorator\nGet Request\nFlask method",
        "Correct": "Route decorator",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "One method can have only one route decorator. True or False?",
        "Answer": "True\nFalse",
        "Correct": "False",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is true about the following line of code?\n\n@api.route(\"/records/<name>\",methods=[\"POST\",\"GET\"])",
        "Answer": "This end-point supports get requests\nThis end-point supports post requests\nThis end-point supports update requests\nThe value of name is variable.",
        "Correct": "This end-point supports get requests\nThis end-point supports post requests\nThe value of name is variable.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 11, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the output of the following code?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\nx=\"Go\"\n\u00a0\nif(x==\"Go\"):\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0print('Go\u00a0')\n\u00a0\nelse:\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0print('Stop')\n\u00a0\nprint('Mike')",
        "Answer": "Go Mike\nMike\nStop Mike",
        "Correct": "Go Mike",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of the following lines of code?\n\n1\n2\nx=1\nx>-5",
        "Answer": "True\nFalse",
        "Correct": "True",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the output of the following few lines of code?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\nx=0\nwhile(x<2):\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0print(x)\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0x=x+1\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0",
        "Answer": "0\n\n1\n0\n\n1\n\n2\n0\n\n1\n\n3\n\n4",
        "Correct": "0\n\n1",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of running the following lines of code ?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\nclass\u00a0Points(object):\n\u00a0\u00a0def\u00a0__init__(self,x,y):\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0self.x=x\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0self.y=y\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0def\u00a0print_point(self):\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0print('x=',self.x,'\u00a0y=',self.y)\n\u00a0\np1=Points(1,2)\np1.print_point()",
        "Answer": "x=1; \n x=1 y=2\ny=2",
        "Correct": " x=1 y=2",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the output of the following few lines of code?\n\n1\n2\nfor\u00a0i,x\u00a0in\u00a0enumerate(['A','B','C']):\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0print(i,2*x)",
        "Answer": "0 AA\n\n1 BB\n\n2 CC\n0 A\n\n1 B\n\n2 C\n0 A\n\n2 B\n\n4 C",
        "Correct": "0 AA\n\n1 BB\n\n2 CC",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the result of running the following lines of code ?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\nclass\u00a0Points(object):\n\u00a0\u00a0def\u00a0__init__(self,x,y):\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0self.x=x\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0self.y=y\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0def\u00a0print_point(self):\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0print('x=',self.x,'\u00a0y=',self.y)\n\u00a0\np2=Points(1,2)\n\u00a0\np2.x=2\n\u00a0\np2.print_point()",
        "Answer": " x=2 y=2\n x=1 y=2\n x=1 y=1",
        "Correct": " x=2 y=2",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consider the function delta, when will the function return a value of 1?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\ndef\u00a0delta(x):\n\u00a0\u00a0if\u00a0x==0:\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0y=1\n\u00a0\u00a0else:\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0y=0\n\u00a0\u00a0return(y)",
        "Answer": " When the input is anything but 0\n When the input is 1\n Never\n When the input is 0",
        "Correct": " When the input is 0",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the output of the following lines of code?\n\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\na=1\n\u00a0\ndef\u00a0do(x):\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0a=100\n\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0return(x+a)\n\u00a0\nprint(do(1))\n\u00a0",
        "Answer": "2\n101\n102",
        "Correct": "101",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Write a function name add that takes two parameter a and b, then return the output of  a + b (Do not use any other variable! You do not need to run it. Only write the code about how you define it.)",
        "Answer": "",
        "Correct": "",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Why is it best practice to have multiple except statements with each type of error labeled correctly?",
        "Answer": "Ensure the error is caught so the program will terminate\nIn order to know what type of error was thrown and the\nlocation within the program\nTo skip over certain blocks of code during execution\nIt is not necessary to label errors",
        "Correct": "In order to know what type of error was thrown and the\nlocation within the program",
        "Title": "Module 3 Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a030 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created GET\u00a0dealer?state=xx action?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created GET\u00a0review?dealerId=num\u00a0action?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created POST review action?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created\u00a0CarModel\u00a0and\u00a0CarMake\u00a0Django models?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you registered\u00a0CarModel\u00a0and\u00a0CarMake\u00a0models with\u00a0Admin site?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created\u00a0new car\u00a0models\u00a0objects with associated car makes and dealerships?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created a `get_dealerships` Django view to get dealer list?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created\u00a0a Django `get_dealer_details` view to get reviews of a dealer?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you updated\u00a0the `get_dealer_details` view to call Watson NLU for analyzing review sentiment?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Have you created `add_review` Django view to post\u00a0a\u00a0dealer review?\u00a0",
        "Answer": "Yes\nNo",
        "Correct": "Yes",
        "Title": "Back End Checklist\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 25, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following statements embeds an image in an HTML document? ",
        "Answer": "<image>link_to_image</image>\n<figure src=\u201dimage URL\u201d>image name</figure>\n<img src=\u201dimage URL\u201d>\n<img href=\u201dimage URL\u201d>image name</img>",
        "Correct": "<img src=\u201dimage URL\u201d>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When defining a hyperlink (<a>), which attribute is used to specify the destination address? ",
        "Answer": "src\ntarget\nhref\nref",
        "Correct": "href",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag CANNOT be used as a container for text? I.e. does not use both an opening <> and closing </> tag",
        "Answer": "<br>\n<p>\n<h1>\n<body>",
        "Correct": "<br>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How are comments written in HTML?",
        "Answer": "\u201c\u201d\u201dThis is a comment\u201d\u201d\u201d\n#This is a comment \n/*This is a comment*/ \n< !-- This is a comment -- > ",
        "Correct": "< !-- This is a comment -- > ",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to denote a cell of data within a table? ",
        "Answer": "<th> \n<tc>\n<td>\n<tr>",
        "Correct": "<td>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is NOT an HTML tag?",
        "Answer": "<p>\n<!DOCTYPE html>\n<article>\n<li>",
        "Correct": "<!DOCTYPE html>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the <br> tag used for?",
        "Answer": "To make text bold\nTo change the text color to brown\nTo change the border\nTo add a line break",
        "Correct": "To add a line break",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following denotes the least important heading?",
        "Answer": "<h1>\n<h6>\n<h10>\n<h5>",
        "Correct": "<h6>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to create an ordered list? ",
        "Answer": "<li>\n<ul>\n<ol>\n<orderedlist>",
        "Correct": "<ol>",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following conditions must be met for scripting to be enabled in browsers? Select one or more options.",
        "Answer": "The browser supports scripting\nAn embedded object is used without the sandbox attribute\nThe browser context has the sandboxed browsing context flag set\nThe user has not disabled scripting for the current browser context",
        "Correct": "The browser supports scripting\nThe user has not disabled scripting for the current browser context",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What best describes the network operations that Node.js makes?",
        "Answer": "Non-blocked operations return immediately without added processing time on the server\nNon-blocked operations return in a synchronized manner with added processing time on the server\nApplications block every network operation to complete at the same time on the server\nBlocked operations return immediately without added processing time on the server",
        "Correct": "Non-blocked operations return immediately without added processing time on the server",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Before the Node.js framework receives the HTTP response message from the remote web server, it immediately returns a result for the http.request function call. What does this result state?",
        "Answer": "The callback function was called successfully.\nThe response message will be sent successfully.\nA request is in progress.\nThe return message will be sent successfully.",
        "Correct": "A request is in progress.",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What parameter is optional in an HTTP request?",
        "Answer": "Event variable parameter\nCallback function parameter\nLocation function parameter\nResource variable parameter",
        "Correct": "Callback function parameter",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What object do Node.js modules in the SDK pass as the first parameter in a callback function?",
        "Answer": "Identity\nDestination\nLocation\nError",
        "Correct": "Error",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What do you pass back in the callback handler to indicate a successful return?",
        "Answer": "Null object\nEmpty string\nError\n404 status code",
        "Correct": "Null object",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which function calls the resultCallback callback function to return results to the main application?",
        "Answer": "http.request()\naggregate_context()\nresult()\nstep()",
        "Correct": "http.request()",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Why can inversion of control be an issue when using callbacks?",
        "Answer": "Inversion of control uses promises which are difficult to implement\nCallbacks sometimes hand over control to third-party code which can make errors hard to identify\nInversion of control creates the need for nested callbacks\nInversion of control is used when something needs to be done sequentially which makes code readability difficult",
        "Correct": "Callbacks sometimes hand over control to third-party code which can make errors hard to identify",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "JSON is the standard format for API data exchange. What relationship does JSON have with Node.js?",
        "Answer": "JSON_SET\nCommon data model folder\nStandard representation of native JavaScript objects\nMetadata file",
        "Correct": "Standard representation of native JavaScript objects",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When an error occurs, which state is the promise at?",
        "Answer": "Rejected\nResolved\nPending\nAborted",
        "Correct": "Rejected",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The axios package handles HTTP requests in Node.js and returns a promise object. The promise object has a method that is called after the promise completes. What method does the promise object use?",
        "Answer": "if\nelse\nthen\nor",
        "Correct": "then",
        "Title": "Graded Quiz\n\nGraded Quiz\n.\n\u00a0\u2022\u00a020 min\n\nDueJun 18, 11:59 PM +07"
    }
]